dnece.com 2005-04-26

# DynamicNursingEducation - Privacy Policy

Privacy Statement  
  
Dynamic nursing Education wants to establish trusting relationships based on respect for personal identity and information. We hope to demonstrate our commitment to our users’ privacy by disclosing our information practices here.   
  
Information Collection  
  
| 

Personal information collected by Dynamic Nursing Education will only be used to conduct business with its customers and will not be sold to or shared with others. 

Registration  
In order to use certain portions of our Web site, a user must first complete our registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address) and unique identifiers (such as, username and password), so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. 

Order  
We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user. 

Surveys & Contests  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information. Such information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Anonymous Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.   
  
Information Use  
  
| 

Profile  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files and clear gifs. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user’s visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share your profile with other third parties. 

Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. Session ID cookie terminate once a user close their browser. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. 

The use of cookies on our site facilitates timesaving features such as remembering passwords or items in a visitor's shopping cart. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site, they will be limited in some areas of our site. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. See the "Profile" section above. 

Log Files  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement. See the "Profile" section above.   
  
Communications from the Site  
  
| 

Special Offers and Updates  
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, specials and an email newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we offer the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" sections below. 

Email Newsletter  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" sections below. 

Tell-A-Friend  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. The friend may contact opt-out of these communications and request the removal of this information from our database. Please see the "Opt-out" section below. 

Service Announcements  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Users may opt-out of these communications as well. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" section below. 

Customer Service  
We communicates with users to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account, we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the user wishes. 

Choice/Opt-out  
Users who no longer wish to receive our email newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of every message or by contacting us directly. 

Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information  
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done on the Registration page or by contacting us directly.   
  
Ownership of Customer Information  
  
| 

Dynamic Nursing Education is the sole owner of the information collected on [www.dynamicnursingeducation.com](http://www.dynamicnursingeducation.com/). Dynamic Nursing Education places a significant value on the information compiled about our registered visitors, and customers. This information is essential to the operation of our company and constitutes a corporate asset of substantial value.   
  
Other Web Site Related Issues  
  
| 

Profile  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files and clear gifs. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user’s visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. We do not share your profile with other third parties. 

Links  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Dynamic Nursing Education, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

Security  
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted. We also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment. 

Notification of Changes  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.   
  
Contact Information  
  
| 

We would be pleased to answer any questions you may have. You may contact us in any of the following ways: 

E-mail: [customerservice@dynamicnursingeducation.com ](mailto:customerservice@dynamicnursingeducation.com%20)  
Phone: 1-714-771-1895   
Mail to: Dynamic Nursing Education  
P.O. Box 1613  
Orange, CA 92856-1613
